[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Lily] Helena Montoya's account, please.
[man] Security, she's here.
[Lily] Your key doesn't work!
Maybe that's what triggered the alarm!
[Mercedes] This is the correct key.
Unless Lily Cruz might have replaced it.
[Raul] Diego Torillo is here,
in Red Dragon's lair.
I want to ask you a favor.
Please take care of the kid.
[Damian] Diego Torillo is a good kid.
You can count on me.
Mercedes told me to keep an eye on you,
so don't give me any trouble.
What are you looking at?
Are you curious about what I'm doing?
[Diego] I'm studying how
I'm going to replace you.
I'm not a lackey like you.
I'm Red Dragon's ally.
Arnaldo! What are you doing?
What's happening to you?!
Lily can answer my questions.
I need to talk to her.
Tell me. What happened? Tell me the truth!
You killed my Nanny Carlotta.
[Damian] Julio Ardiente's still after you.
The violence won't stop,
no matter whose camp you join.
It could be worse for you now
since you sided with Red Dragon.
[Jepoy] Red Dragon will use
Diego against you, Lily.
She could use Diego
against Julio Ardiente.
[Diego] What's that for?
[Helena] I want you to kill Lily Cruz.
Diego.
Here's the blue book.
All of Red Dragon's clients
are listed there.
I'll have her hideout raided.
What's important is we take down
Red Dragon and the Ardientes!
I promise you, I'll be fine.
Diego, please.
Don't go back there anymore.
[tense music playing]
-Is this real?
-Yes, Red Dragon.
Shut up!
They look legit.
According to this website,
Lily Cruz did book a flight.
So, what are you waiting for?
I have a concert to do tonight.
Do not disturb me. Go after Lily Cruz!
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Oh!
Criminal case number N17-455…
Dismissed based on
lack of witnesses and evidence.
[laughs]
The case against me is dismissed.
Which means…
I will be going back to the capitol
to claim my rightful title
as governor of Ardiente!
[laughing]
How sweet it is!
Great news! Great news, Papa!
Yes.
But you know what?
Tell that to a garbage bin.
That's where you'll find
tons of "plastic!"
Look, Papa. I am genuinely happy for you.
-[scoffs]
-But you know, Papa?
With all the lawsuits against you,
I doubt you'll ever be reinstated.
Anything can happen.
Oh, yes. Of course. Anything can happen.
Including me offering you
a position in government.
Come on, Papa. Save the sweet talk.
You never offered me anything.
In fact, you're the reason
I was removed from power,
whereas Mama offered me a seat
in her group.
And with all the lawsuits
and controversies
surrounding your victory,
I doubt you'll be reinstated as governor.
So, don't count your chickens
before they hatch, Papa.
[scoffs] We'll see.
But suddenly, I just came up
with the greatest idea.
The brightest one at that.
I know the perfect affair where
I will declare my reinstatement.
And it's going to happen with a bang!
[tense music playing]
Ridiculous. This is impossible, Attorney.
Julio Ardiente can't be reinstated.
This is not the end of it.
So, that's it?
Everything we've done to oust
Julio Ardiente was for nothing?
Our efforts just went down the drain?
What would Lily say?
We'll review this, Camia.
This is not over.
No, Attorney. Diego was right.
Let's stop fighting the clean way.
Helena Montoya has a concert tonight.
I'm sure Julio Ardiente will be there.
We'll fight for the truth there.
Mama, the case was dismissed.
Relax. Your father hasn't
been reinstated yet.
Mama, you know how he works.
He's got connections.
He can easily get off the hook. Besides,
he said he'll make us kneel
once he becomes the governor.
[chuckles]
Emilia, my princess.
Don't be such a worrier.
Nothing's happened yet.
You're dampening my spirits.
Well, if it's war that your father wants,
it's war that I'm going to give him.
Please take them to the car, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
-Love.
-Yes?
Maybe it's better if you just stay here.
Don't come with us.
I can't, love. I need to go
to Auntie Camia's protest.
Something might happen.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Just stay here.
I didn't know you were
a strict boyfriend, Jepoy.
But with everything
that's been happening lately,
I have to be there for them.
So, don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
You'll be there too, right?
Shouldn't you be supporting me
in our fight?
Remember, you're one
of the people Lily can count on.
Okay, fine, fine.
Please allow me to go.
Just don't leave my side, okay?
I won't.
-Promise?
-Promise.
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues playing]
What is it, love? Is something wrong?
I just feel like…
someone's watching us.
Where?
That's right, Anna.
You should be very afraid.
Because you're my next target.
Are you ready?
It's probably nothing.
You should stop being paranoid, love.
As long as you're with me,
you'll always be safe.
[groans]
Damn it, Jepoy.
What did you see in that woman?
Can't you see that she is obviously
a total downgrade from me?
Can't you see that?
I'd get it if she satisfies your needs.
Which I assume she doesn't.
Natalie, what the hell are you doing here?
What the hell is going on?
Can you just stop? You're going insane.
You just need a distraction, Natalie.
That's all you need.
Just stop.
Red Dragon, huh?
I've been wanting to join
your group for a while now.
Well, why don't I stop thinking
about it and just do it?
[crowd cheering]
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you!
Thank you. I'm glad to be back!
Thank you very much!
Thank you to all of you.
Thank you very much.
-What are you doing here?
-Oh, good morning.
Actually, I should be the one
asking you that question.
What are you doing here?
Security, why did you let him in?
Apprehend him!
It's all right, boys. Stay.
Sit.
Behave.
I don't think your
security force has the right
nor the power to remove me
from this premises
because you are now talking
to the newly reinstated
governor of this place we call home.
The decision is not yet official.
Ah! Official, official, my foot.
All that's missing is the date
of my reinstatement.
And so, it's official when I say so.
And today, in front
of all these witnesses.
That's why it's official. Isn't it?
Oh, by the way, I noticed you
were on your way to my office.
I think your office
is way on the other side.
Because I remembered passing by,
and I saw it was written on the door.
"Vice Governor Mateo".
And down here
is the office of the governor,
which is me, Julio Ardiente.
You know, Mateo?
As far as I can remember,
I never rented out my seat.
I didn't lease it out.
The governor's chair
belongs to me and me alone.
It's mine. It's very much mine.
And I don't feel like
sharing it with anyone.
So, I would suggest
you go back to your office,
I will be in my office,
and should there be any need
for us to talk further,
I will call for you.
Don't call me. I'll call you.
Okay, Vice?
I'll see you around.
[Julio] Arnaldo!
Arnaldo, my grandson!
Your grandpa is here!
I've got good news for you.
Come on!
Arnaldo, get changed! We're going out!
We're going to watch a concert
and celebrate.
Because your grandpa, the king
of Ardiente, is back on top!
[Julio laughs]
-What the-- Nico!
-Yes, Governor.
-What happened?
-Governor, it's Mayor Arnaldo!
Arnaldo!
-Arnaldo!
-Mayor Arnaldo!
Arnaldo!
Arnaldo, wake up!
What happened to you?
Look at you. You look like dirt.
Well? What happened to you?
Arnaldo, I'm talking to you.
Grandpa, it's…
-It's Lily.
-Huh?
Lily said…
Lily said I killed her Nanny Carlotta.
Is that true? Did I do that?
Huh?
-No.
-Did I kill her?
-Am I a bad person?
-No. You are not a bad person.
-And this stops now!
-Am I bad?
I did not kill…
I killed someone. But I'm not a killer.
No. No.
I'm not a killer.
I'm not a killer. I'm not.
That's enough. This has to stop.
It's time for you to come home.
You'll come to the mansion
whether you like it or not.
-Why would I kill…
-Nico, help him up.
Yes, sir.
-Mayor.
-Stand up!
This place smells like crap!
Come on! Let's take him home.
Let's go.
Let's leave this… I don't know
what to call this place!
[tense music playing]
Everyone listen.
These are the weapons we'll be using
at Madam Red Dragon's concert.
Diego, Romulo.
This is the list of targets
Red Dragon invited,
who could be the keys to Julio
Ardiente's reinstatement.
We will dispatch them all. Understand?
[Diego] All of them?
We'll kill all of them?
Well, if Red Dragon says kill them all,
we kill them all.
[tense music playing]
Double-check the blue book, Romulo.
If Red Dragon's allies show up,
seat them all together,
away from where we'll open fire.
[upbeat music playing]
Where's Diego? Diego!
Put that down!
[thuds]
I'm sorry. I thought it was mine.
Diego, where's the blue book?
[tense music playing]
Is this what you're looking for?
Where did you get that?
Unlike you, I know how to
keep things safe and hidden.
Diego made a copy of the blue
book before he gave it to me.
We can use that, dear.
But, Lily, what's your plan?
Diego said Red Dragon alerted the airport,
the same airport
where they think you'll be.
Red Dragon's people are probably
on their way there right now.
Don't worry about it, Mom.
I alerted the police
about the entrapment operation.
When the Dragon Ladies get there,
they're ours.
Okay, but what will happen at
Helena Montoya's event tonight?
[tense music playing]
Hello, Miss Mercedes.
-Who the hell are you?
-I'm Natalie.
And you are Mercedes Palacio.
Am I correct?
I have no time to be chatting
with strangers.
Let's go.
Hang on, wait. Um…
Well, actually, it's okay
if you don't know who I am.
What's important is I know who you are.
I did my research.
And I know your dirty little secret.
[chuckles]
I know who you work for.
You work for the queen, Red Dragon?
Am I right?
Please get this woman out of my way.
Uh-uh!
[chuckles]
Don't touch me.
I didn't come here as your enemy.
I came here as your ally.
And, possibly, we can work together.
I have a lot of money
and I have the resources.
All I need is a meeting with your boss.
And I'm sure she'd be
interested in working with me.
So, make it happen.
[chuckles]
I think you're lost, Miss…
Whatever your name is.
First off, I'm not involved
with this "Red Dragon."
Second, I'm not involved in the sex trade.
Excuse me?
So, if you're trying to apply
as a prostitute,
go online.
Sluts are high-tech nowadays.
With that said, you can either
leave on your own,
or I'll have those two
drag you out of here.
Goodbye.
I'll be seeing you again, Mercedes.
[chuckles]
[Mercedes] Let's go.
Mercedes.
Mr. Oscar. What a surprise.
How did you find me?
I have my ways.
[Mercedes] Well, what brought
you here, sir?
I need to talk to… you know who.
Oh, Mr. Oscar.
The Madam is quite busy at the moment.
But I can set an appointment
so you two can talk.
The NBI raided my operations.
I lost millions.
And that's why I need
to talk to the Madam.
Sir Oscar, just relax.
The Madam will find a way out of this.
I'll just call you, okay?
Let's go.
[Mercedes] So you have to take note of
every instruction I give you.
-Let's go? Come.
-Okay.
[easy music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
Okay, so, as we discussed
at the briefing earlier,
you will have your designated
posts inside the venue.
I need you to be in your
individual positions as planned.
-Is that clear?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay. You may go.
Miss Cruz, why are you sabotaging
Miss Helena Montoya's benefit concert?
The Ardientes are just using that concert
to cover up major issues,
such as the pending cases
against Julio Ardiente.
He's been charged with homicide,
theft, and electoral fraud.
So, there's no way
we're going to let him reign
as governor ever again.
[tense music playing]
Well, Madam Emilia, you are looking good.
Your gown brings out your eyes.
Thank you, Mercedes.
But I know you're just saying that
because you want to gain
back my Mama's favor,
now that I'm her right-hand woman.
So, with that, you have to obey
every word that I tell you.
Actually, just for this event.
Not for the entire operation.
Oh, no.
For this event and… suspiciously,
why isn't Lily Cruz here?
As a matter of fact, I know
she's flying out of the country,
and my people are already after her.
[scoffs]
Mercedes, Mama did make the
right decision to replace you.
You are silly and naïve.
How could you believe her
when she said she was leaving?
She fooled us before, remember?
Everyone thought she was dead.
But look at her now. She's still alive.
So, if I were you, Mercedes,
I wouldn't believe her
when she says she's already
making her way to the airport
because she could just be
setting you all up.
Piece of advice.
As long as you haven't seen her
boarding the plane
with your own eyes,
don't believe that she's leaving.
Because Lily Cruz never flees.
And more importantly, she never dies.
Excuse me.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Please, be seated inside.
Hello.
There are seats inside just for you.
Please, be seated inside.
Good evening.
Hi!
Enjoy the show.
[suspenseful music playing]
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Diego.
I'm trying to get an update
from the Dragon Ladies
I sent to the airport.
They aren't picking up.
Okay. I'll cover for you here.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo, my son.
Wow! Look at you. You look so great.
Are you okay now? Are you feeling better?
-Yeah.
-I'm okay. I'm okay.
-He was able to rest at home.
-That's good to know.
Um…
I still have a lot of questions,
but Grandpa said,
if I came tonight,
I might get some answers.
Yes, that's right.
And you'll finally get to bond
with your grandmother.
Isn't that lovely?
-I guess.
-So, shall we go?
[Magbanua] Governor, wait.
The protest they were planning…
Camia Cruz went through with it.
[scoffs]
-Thank you, Miss Cruz.
-Thank you.
Camia, is there anything I can do to help?
We've got it covered.
But thank you for coming.
I'll do anything for you and Lily.
Don't mind them.
They can't stop me
from getting my position back.
Women like Camia Cruz
are only good for housework.
Cooking, doing the laundry,
taking care of children.
But when it comes to politics,
I'll swallow her whole.
Let's go.
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
[protesters] Step down, Julio Ardiente!
Julio Ardiente is a cheater!
Step down, Julio Ardiente!
[protesters continue chanting]
[phone buzzing]
Diego, listen carefully.
[protesters continue chanting]
[tense music playing]
[phone buzzing]
[knocks]
[sighs]
[Emilia] Mama!
-Look at you. You are so…
-Emilia!
…beautiful, Mama!
-Thank you.
-Everything's ready.
So, they're all waiting for you.
That's great, darling.
-So, are you ready, Mama?
-Yes, I am.
-Okay. I shall cue them.
-Okay.
-I'll wait for you inside, Mama.
-Great.
-Break a leg, Mama!
-Thank you, Emilia.
-You're so beautiful.
-Thank you.
See you around, Mama.
[Helena sighs]
Is this confirmed?
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Mercedes?
-Madam…
The Dragon Ladies have been
arrested by the police.
What?!
They are questioning them about you.
They already know you're Red Dragon.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia] Tonight, we are
celebrating the anniversary
of Helena Montoya's Foundation
with music and magic.
With her friends and
beneficiaries of her foundation,
without further ado, let's welcome
the one and only Helena Montoya.
[applause]
["Maging Sino Ka Man"
instrumental playing]
I just can't believe you let
the Dragon Ladies get arrested.
You know, you're ruining
Mama's special night.
Shut up, Emilia,
if you don't want me to take
my frustration out on you.
Wow! [chuckles]
You just fell into Lily's trap.
You really are stupid.
[applause]
Please, sit down. Please, sit down.
Thank you very much.
[ominous music]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[Helena] Hello. Good evening, friends.
It is such an honor to be in the presence
of very prestigious guests.
And I must say that I am deeply honored,
and I am humbled,
not only by your presence,
but of your gift of love and generosity.
This night is especially for
the people of Ardiente
because all proceeds from this event
will go straight to them.
So, thank you so much for your
very early Christmas gift.
Give yourselves a round of applause.
[applause]
I would also like to thank
my special guests.
Business tycoon Salvador Tatad.
Let's all give him a big hand.
[applause]
Former senator Isagani Bacaro.
And former ambassador Horacio Perez.
[applause]
Thank you all very much for
making this evening possible.
And, of course, I'd like to thank
my only daughter,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
Let's all give her a big hand too.
She single-handedly
organized tonight's event.
Thank you very much.
You are the reason
for my calling to help
the people of Ardiente.
And, finally, the reason
we are all here this evening.
To the one with an unbreakable spirit
and a very passionate heart.
To the one whose name
will never be forgotten.
Ladies and gentlemen, I recognize the one,
the only…
[ominous music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[upbeat music continues playing]
Lily Cruz.
Oh, yes. I am the one.
The only one.
Lily, what are you doing here?
In just a few seconds,
you're all about to receive
a message on your phones.
And these messages will reveal
Helena Montoya's true identity.
[tense music playing]
[phones chiming]
I'm one of the Dragon Ladies
who worked for Red Dragon's organization.
And, I guarantee you,
that Red Dragon is none other
than Helena Montoya.
[tense music playing]
-What's going on?
-Mama.
Red Dragon's organization possesses
over 50 billion pesos worth of assets.
Though, we all know her more
by the name, Helena Montoya.
Her organization thrives
on the support of her clients,
who also hide behind masks.
[dramatic music]
Her number one client is none
other than Salvador Tatad,
a businessman who acts as a
middleman for terrorist groups.
Her next client is Isagani Bacaro.
Stop it! Stop this nonsense!
Mercedes, please do something.
Why are you laughing?
Why aren't you helping us?
You know, you don't really care for us.
Why should I care?
No one cared for me
when I was in the gutters.
Well, now that you're talking
to the most powerful man
in the land of Ardiente,
I couldn't care less about you
and your mother.
I wouldn't even lift a finger,
even if it meant
your life was on the line.
"Most powerful man in Ardiente?"
What are you talking about?
[laughs]
Emilia, Emilia.
The answer's so close,
it's about to bite you.
I am the new governor of this province.
That's right.
You don't have to be surprised.
And today is the day of my reinstatement.
Sorry to steal the thunder
from your mother.
While I'm on my way up,
she's sinking all the way down.
Isn't life amazing?
Just a few months ago, I was down and out.
Now, I'm up and about.
Down and out. Up and about.
That rhymes!
Don't you feel the itch, you…
No, I wouldn't call you that.
You're my daughter! I love you.
[laughs]
Excuse me.
Arnaldo?
Don't look at me.
Well, Helena!
Welcome to my world!
It's the kind that can't stand
criminals like you.
[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Lily Cruz.
Who-- Who are you?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
You bastard!
You monster!
[gunshots]
[indistinct shouting]
Stand back! Get him!
Now, tell me the truth.
-Answer me!
-Yes! I am!
I am Lily Cruz!
I am Lily Cruz! I am Lily Cruz!
Lily?
-[chuckles] Ivy.
-Lily Cruz.
-That's my name.
-No. It's Ivy Aguas.
It's Lily Cruz.
Lily Cruz.
Did you have something to do
with what happened to me?
[sighs]
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you inside?
[tense music playing]
What about you? What are you doing here?
I knew it.
There's something off about you.
What are you up to?
What do you want from Red Dragon?
[tense music playing]
You know what? You have a marvelous voice.
You're a great singer.
But I think you're a better actress
in a "playing innocent" role.
But I regret to tell you,
your show is over.
Curtain call!
The jig is up because right now,
everyone here knows that Helena Montoya
is none other than Red Dragon.
[mouthing] What?
[tense music playing]
[inaudible]
[ominous music swelling]
I will not allow someone
like Lily Cruz to slander me.
This Lily Cruz just did it.
[Asuncion] Helena Montoya,
you are under arrest
for arms trafficking
and human trafficking.
-Please come with us.
-Wait! Wait!
-You cannot do this to my Mama!
-Let go of me!
[Julio] The mother and her daughter,
both taken down by a wildflower.
Looks like you have something
planned for Lily Cruz.
I am above the law.
No, wait. I am the law.
And that Lily Cruz just declared
a full-fledged war
against Red Dragon.
[theme music playing]